Guide to the Photographs by and relating to Allen Ginsberg MSS.PHOTO.0450
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Contact Sheets, Series 2
  - Contact sheet 932, 1988 Jan. 19; 932 (Item 19)
    "Jerusalem, Israel; Wailing Wall"
  - Contact sheet 933, 1988 Jan. 19; 933 (Item 19)
    "Jerusalem, Israel; Wall of Jerusalem"
  - Contact sheet 934, 1988 Jan. 19; 934 (Item 19)
    "Jerusalem, Israel; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 935, 1988 Jan. 21; 935 (Item 19)
    "Tel Aviv, Israel; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; "
  - Contact sheet 936, 1988 Jan. 24; 936 (Item 19)
    "Haifa, Israel; "
  - Contact sheet 937, 1988 Jan. 27; 937 (Item 19)
    "Tel Aviv, Israel"
  - Contact sheet 938, 1988 Jan. 27; 938 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 939, 1988 Jan. 30; 939 (Item 19)
    "Tel Aviv, Israel; New York City; airport scenes; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 940, 1988 Feb. 1; 940 (Item 19)
    New York City; kitchen window views; street scenes with peddlers
  - Contact sheet 941, 1988 Feb. 6; 941 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 942, 1988 Feb. 7; 942 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 943, 1988 Feb. 2; 943 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 944, 1988 Feb. 12; 944 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 945, 1988 Feb. 19; 945 (Item 19)
    New York City; Harry Smith with string figures
  - Contact sheet 946, 1988 Feb. 20; 946 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 947, 1987 Dec. 1; 947 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 948, 1988 Mar. 3; 948 (Item 19)
    "New York City; Milwaukee, WI; mall scenes; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 949, 1988 Feb. 22; 949 (Item 19)
    "New York City; Washington, DC; Lucien Carr on boat in DC; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 950, 1988 Mar. 10; 950 (Item 19)
    "Paterson, NJ; Buffalo, NY; New York City"
  - Contact sheet 951, 1988 Mar. 15; 951 (Item 19)
    New York City; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; Mary Help of Christians Church window
  - Contact sheet 952, 1988 Mar. 14; 952 (Item 19)
    "Cambridge, MA"
  - Contact sheet 953, 1988 Mar. 19; 953 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 954, 1988 Mar. 26; 954 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 955, 1988 Mar. 30; 955 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 957, 1988 Apr. 10; 957 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 958, 1988 Apr. 14; 958 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 959, 1988 Apr. 21; 959 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 960, 1988 Apr. 29; 960 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 961, 1988 May 1; 961 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 962, 1988 May 1; 962 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 979, 1986 July 1; 979 (Item 19)
    "COLOR: New York City; Lawrence, KS; Allen Ginsberg self portrait in bathroom mirror, Burroughs' sink; cops and altercation by church E. 12th St., NY"
  - Contact sheet 980, 1986 July 1; 980 (Item 19)
    COLOR: New York City; Columbia College
  - Contact sheet 981, 1987 Mar. 16; 981 (Item 19)
    "New York City; Paterson, NJ; Paterson street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 982, 1987 Mar. 23; 982 (Item 19)
    New York City; Peter Orlovsky at Brooklyn College
  - Contact sheet 983, 1987 Mar. 23; 983 (Item 19)
    "New York City; Halifax, Canada; Peter Orlovsky at Brooklyn College"
  - Contact sheet 984, 1988 Jan. 15; 984 (Item 19)
    New York City; kitchen window views; American Academy
    American Academy
  - Contact sheet 985, 1988 May 7; 985 (Item 19)
    New York City; kitchen window views; DCTV Downtown TV
  - Contact sheet 986, 1988 May 14; 986 (Item 19)
    New York City; kitchen window views; multiple vitamins in store
    Philip Glass
  - Contact sheet 987, 1988 May 18; 987 (Item 19)
    New York City; American Academy; subway views
  - Contact sheet 988, 1988 May 22; 988 (Item 19)
    "San Francisco, CA; 1367 Grant Ave."
    Shig Murao
  - Contact sheet 989, 1988 May 22; 989 (Item 19)
    "San Francisco, CA; San Jose, CA; Motel, San Jose; doorway City Lights"
  - Contact sheet 990, 1988 May 23; 990 (Item 19)
    "San Francisco, CA; Kaliflower Commune"
  - Contact sheet 991, 1988 May 23; 991 (Item 19)
    "San Francisco, CA; Kaliflower Commune; Demo, Saturday Soup Kitchen Entertainment"
  - Contact sheet 992, 1988 May 23; 992 (Item 19)
    "San Francisco, CA; Anonymous Chinese Waiters eating?; City Lights cash desk"
  - Contact sheet 993, 1988 May 23; 993 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 994, 1988 May 23; 994 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 995, 1988 May 27; 995 (Item 19)
    "Bedrock Mortar/Kitkitdizze, CA"
  - Contact sheet 996, 1988 May 28; 996 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 997, 1988 May 28; 997 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 998, 1988 May 28; 998 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 999, 1988 May 28; 999 (Item 19)
  - Contact sheet 1001, 1988 May 30; 1001 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1002, 1988 May 30; 1002 (Item 20)
    "Bedrock Mortar/Kitkitdizze, CA; "
  - Contact sheet 1003, 1988 May 30; 1003 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1005, 1988 Jun. 3; 1005 (Item 20)
    "Bedrock Mortar/Kitkitdizze, and San Francisco, CA; Bedrock Mortar"
  - Contact sheet 1006, 1988 Jun. 3; 1006 (Item 20)
    "Bedrock Mortar/Kitkitdizze, CA; outhouse at Bedrock Mortar"
    Paul Grady; Gen Snyder
  - Contact sheet 1007, 1988 Jun. 3; 1007 (Item 20)
    "San Francisco, CA; Cafe Trieste; Tivoli; Blue Coral Reef reading; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1008, 1988 Jun. 8; 1008 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1009, 1009 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1010, 1988 July 4; 1010 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1011, 1988 July 4; 1011 (Item 20)
    "Lowell, MA; Lowell celebrates Kerouac; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1012, 1988 July 4; 1012 (Item 20)
    "Lowell, MA; Lowell celebrates Kerouac Memorial; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1013, 1988 July 4; 1013 (Item 20)
    "Lowell, MA; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1014, 1988 May 10; 1014 (Item 20)
    New York City; Romanian Writers' Union and translator from USA; kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 1015, 1988 June 7; 1015 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1016, 1988 July 6; 1016 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1017, 1988 July 7; 1017 (Item 20)
    "Boulder, CO; 2 AM nude"
  - Contact sheet 1018, 1988 July 9; 1018 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1019, 1988 July 9; 1019 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1020, 1988 July 9; 1020 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1021, 1988 July 9; 1021 (Item 20)
    "Boulder, CO; Mark Ewert nude"
  - Contact sheet 1022, 1988 July 9; 1022 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1023, 1988 July 13; 1023 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1024, 1988 July 14; 1024 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1025, 1988 July 16; 1025 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1026, 1988 July 16; 1026 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1027, 1988 July 16; 1027 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1028, 1988 July 16; 1028 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1029, 1988 July 17; 1029 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1030, 1988 July 17; 1030 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1031, 1988 July 20; 1031 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1032, 1988 July 20; 1032 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1033, 1988 July 20; 1033 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1034, 1988 July 23; 1034 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1035, 1988 July 23; 1035 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1036, 1988 July 24; 1036 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1037, 1988 July 24; 1037 (Item 20)
    Mark Ewert
  - Contact sheet 1038, 1988 July 24; 1038 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1039, 1988 June 9; 1039 (Item 20)
    "New York City; Hamburg, Germany; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 1040, 1988 June 11; 1040 (Item 20)
    "Hamburg, Germany"
  - Contact sheet 1041, 1988 June 12; 1041 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1042, 1988 June 15; 1042 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1043, 1988 June 16; 1043 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1044, 1988 June 16; 1044 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1045, 1988 June 20; 1045 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1046, 1988 June 23; 1046 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1047, 1988 July 30; 1047 (Item 20)
    Edith Ginsberg
  - Contact sheet 1048, 1988 July 30; 1048 (Item 20)
    "Paterson, NJ; Boulder, CO"
  - Contact sheet 1049, 1988 July 30; 1049 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1050, 1988 July 30; 1050 (Item 20)
    "Paterson, NJ; New York City; Boulder, CO; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 1051, 1988 July 31; 1051 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1052, 1988 July 31; 1052 (Item 20)
    "New York City; Paterson, NJ; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1053, 1988 Aug. 6; 1053 (Item 20)
    New York City; Tompkins Square Park; kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 1054, 1988 Aug. 6; 1054 (Item 20)
    New York City; Tompkins Square Park
  - Contact sheet 1055, 1988 Aug. 8; 1055 (Item 20)
    New York City; Tompkins Square Park; subway scenes
  - Contact sheet 1056, 1988 Aug. 10; 1056 (Item 20)
    New York City; Tompkins Square Park; street scenes
  - Contact sheet 1057, 1988 Aug. 10; 1057 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1058, 1988 Aug. 13; 1058 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1059, 1988 Sept. 3; 1059 (Item 20)
    "Atlanta, GA; dining mall off Peachtree St.; inside Atlanta crude garden sculpture baseball player and cerest; Howard Finster's Paradise Garden"
  - Contact sheet 1060, 1988 Sept. 3; 1060 (Item 20)
    "New York City; Atlanta, GA; Ai Wei Wei on Ave. A and 8th or 7th St.; Signs Ave. A; street construction; 11th St. and Ave A N.E. corner where Subterranean Paradise Alley was now parking lot w/graffiti; Funeral Home Ave A and 12th S.W. corner; Chinese Restaurant on 3rd Ave, Ai Wei Wei and NE corner near St. Marks Place, sculptor painter friend and owner of restaurant; kitchen window views; Bei Dao and wife Sho Fi; pickets at Last Temptation of Christ; airport to Atlanta?"
  - Contact sheet 1061, 1988 Sept. 5; 1061 (Item 20)
    "New York City; Atlanta, GA; Howard Finster's Paradise Garden with Mark Ewert and his friend Betsy; with Ewert's mother at King Memorial Center; Atlanta Bum's bottles, weeds and skyscraper; Mark Ewert and Allen Ginsberg on walkway with skyscraper; kitchen window views; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1062, 1988 Sept. 10; 1062 (Item 20)
    "New York City; homeless drunks 14th St. and Ave. A; Steven Taylor at Guitar Fair, Mary Help of Christians Church; promoters of Guitar Fair; Steven Taylor trying out guitar, highbricking (double) pickup; corner 13th and 1st Ave.; near south east corner 12th and 1st Ave. on 12th St.; street scenes; kitchen window views; graffiti"
  - Contact sheet 1063, 1988 Sept. 16; 1063 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1064, 1988 Sept. 21; 1064 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1065, 1988 Aug. 20; 1065 (Item 20)
    New York City; street scenes; 437 E. 12th St. apartment building; Harley
  - Contact sheet 1066, 1988 Aug. 13; 1066 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1067, 1988 Oct. 1; 1067 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1068, 1988 Oct. 6; 1068 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1069, 1988 Oct. 6; 1069 (Item 20)
    New York City; graffiti; Francesco Clemente's loft
  - Contact sheet 1070, 1988 Oct. 7; 1070 (Item 20)
    New York City; Francesco Clemente's loft
  - Contact sheet 1071, 1988 Oct. 11; 1071 (Item 20)
    "New York City; Paterson, NJ; Paterson mills and falls"
  - Contact sheet 1072, 1988 Oct. 11; 1072 (Item 20)
    New York City; at the Kiev restaurant
  - Contact sheet 1073, 1988 Oct. 11; 1073 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1074, 1988 Oct. 11; 1074 (Item 20)
  - Contact sheet 1075, 1988 Oct. 14; 1075 (Item 20)
    "New York City; Boston, MA; taxi cab scene"
  - Contact sheet 1077, 1988 Oct. 15; 1077 (Item 21)
    "New York City; Boston, MA"
  - Contact sheet 1078, 1988 Oct. 17; 1078 (Item 21)
    New York City; Bob Dylan onstage; kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 1079, 1988 Oct. 18; 1079 (Item 21)
    "Tokyo, Japan"
  - Contact sheet 1081, 1988 Oct. 21; 1081 (Item 21)
    "Tokyo, Japan; street scenes"
    S. Tanehana
  - Contact sheet 1082.1, 1988 Oct. 21; 1082.1 (Item 21)
    "Tokyo, Japan; Tokyo Theatre Poetry Reading; Butoh Party; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
    Tokyo Theatre; Ginsberg, Allen
  - Contact sheet 1082.2, 1988 Oct. 26; 1082.2 (Item 21)
    "COLOR: Tokyo, Japan; Oshikamura; Benjo nite; Kamoyama Village; street scenes; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; "
  - Contact sheet 1083, 1988 Oct. 22; 1083 (Item 21)
    "Tokyo, Japan; New York City; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; airplane views; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 1084, 1988 Oct. 25; 1084 (Item 21)
    "Tokyo, Japan; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1085, 1988 Oct. 25; 1085 (Item 21)
    "Tokyo, Japan; Railroad station; Akihabara, Tokyo farewell; 2-5 Nanao Sakaki in Literary Museum Garden, Tokyo; 7 Sogyu Fukumura, Hidetoshi Tomiyama, Allen Ginsberg, Nanao Sakaki, Folk Art Museum Tokyo; 8 Sogyu in alley; 9-10 Kayuko Shiraishi at reception after American Literary Society Sun. Oct. 23 reading; and Nanao Sakaki and Sogyu reading; 12-13 AG & ?Christine Sushat? Oct. 23; 15-16 Suwa Yu Oct. 23; 17-18 Subway Suwa Yu and Simon Suchat Oct. 23; 19-20 Suwa Yu and student and Simon Suchat Oct. 23; 20-25 Electronic section Tokyo: Akchabara signs Oct. 24; 26-28 Mrs. Watari and her gallery sign Oct. 24; 29-33 Watari Gallery interview press conference; 35-36 railroad station leaving Tokyo Sogyu, Nanao, editor of ecological magazine"
  - Contact sheet 1086, 1988 Oct. 27; 1086 (Item 21)
    "Oshikamura Ridge, Japan; Southern Mountains"
  - Contact sheet 1087, 1988 Oct. 28; 1087 (Item 21)
    "Tokyo, Japan; Tokyo to Lake Siwa, Mt. Hiei, Sogyu; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1088, 1988 Oct. 28; 1088 (Item 21)
    "Tokyo, Japan; Mihuma Nuke Plant; Myosugi Temple"
    Nanao Sakaki
  - Contact sheet 1089, 1988 Oct. 30; 1089 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1090, 1988 Oct. 31; 1090 (Item 21)
    "Kyoto, Japan; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1091, 1988 Oct. 31; 1091 (Item 21)
    "Kyoto, Japan; train window, Osaka Kyoto Express; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1092, 1988 Oct. 31; 1092 (Item 21)
    "Osaka, Japan; Korean market; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1093, 1988 Oct. 25; 1093 (Item 21)
    "COLOR: Tokyo, Japan; 0-2 Jirha Wein, Kamayawa, Oshikamura, Shimoina Gen, Nagans-ken Japan Southern Alps; 2-4 musician "Bobo" from Oshihamura Village, Kamiyawa settlement, leaving for walk in woods; 5-22 "Komorebi" (sunlight sifting thru trees' leaves branches), Karamayu (larch) tree woods, 6A Katsura tree (grows together) old, akebi purple fruit; 17A Jirha Wein, camera lady, Bob O, Nanao Sakaki in virgin woods, southern mountains, above Oshihamura village; 23-24 mushroom soup for Kamiyawa folk picnic; 29-34 picnic southern mts background, Nanao; 36 in Vayo Village, near Futsitokuji (temple) (King of Medicine Mt. Temple) Generosity Temple"
  - Contact sheet 1094, 1988 Oct. 27; 1094 (Item 21)
    "COLOR: Tokyo, Japan; Southern Mountains Japan (Oct. 27-30); at Jiri Wein's outhouse light 7-12, Kamiyawa Village, Oshikamura, Shimoina Gun, Nagano-ken; 7-9 Jiri Wein's Abachi room and porch; 11-13 overlooking Lake Biwa and Mt. Hiei, Sogyu Fukumara and camera lady; 14-16 Mihema Nuke Power Plant Control room, Kansai Power Co. near Obama, Japan Sea, Sogyu Fukumura, Nanao Sakaki, Idaka Tsuneo Zen priest; #16 with radishes, Mihama Nuke plant turrets background, 19-24 Osaka peace march, anti Nuke march"
  - Contact sheet 1095, 1988 Oct. 30; 1095 (Item 21)
    "COLOR: Tokyo, Japan; Osaka Anti-Nuke March (Oct. 30) Nanao Sakaki and Sogyu Fukumura; 10-15A Korean market, Osaka; 11A Sogyu, Nanao and Jodo Priest of Tenryu-in Shu-Kai Kono & wife Etzuko (in red), w/camera facing me; 16A counting money Korean market Osaka; 20-23 main Kyoto U. Street, Kyoto Oct. 30, 1988"
  - Contact sheet 1096, 1988 Oct. 30; 1096 (Item 21)
    "COLOR: Kyoto, Japan; Birthday Party for Nanao, Sogyu and Idaha Tsuneo; birthday party for bar, Chris Pearce 25; Ryooaji Garden 26-29; First Zen Institute library background 30-36 Matsunami Tai-Um new priest; Gion lights 33-36"
  - Contact sheet 1097, 1988 Nov. 3; 1097 (Item 21)
    "COLOR: Kyoto, Japan; New York City; Pachinko 0-2; #3-7 Nanao Sakaki reading at Seebu Kodo Hall, Kyoto University; 8-10 after performance party; 11-20 Kyoto Bus to Osaka airport with Sogyu, Nanao and Matoki Noike, nature conservancy of Japan; 21-31 Mt. Fuji in cloud first time I saw it; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 1098, 1988 Nov. 10; 1098 (Item 21)
    COLOR: New York City; kitchen window views; Vicki Stanbury's friend
  - Contact sheet 1099, 1988 Nov. 1; 1099 (Item 21)
    "Kyoto, Japan; Diaminji Mt., Press Conference"
  - Contact sheet 1100, 1988 Nov. 24; 1100 (Item 21)
    "New York City; LI, NY; Thanksgiving at Eugene and Connie Brooks;"
  - Contact sheet 1101, 1988 Nov. 1; 1101 (Item 21)
    "Kyoto, Japan"
  - Contact sheet 1102, 1988 Nov. 2; 1102 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1103, 1988 Nov. 3; 1103 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1104, 1988 Nov. 6; 1104 (Item 21)
    "Kyoto, Japan; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1105, 1988 Nov. 6; 1105 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1106, 1988 Nov. 8; 1106 (Item 21)
    New York City; kitchen window views; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; homeless
  - Contact sheet 1107, 1988 Nov. 10; 1107 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1108, 1988 Nov. 11; 1108 (Item 21)
    Chaim and Rene Gross
  - Contact sheet 1109, 1988 Nov. 12; 1109 (Item 21)
    "New York City; Paterson, NJ; Paterson falls; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 1110, 1988 Nov. 15; 1110 (Item 21)
    New York City; Chinese poets at Museum of Modern Art
    Simon Pettet; Museum of Modern Art
  - Contact sheet 1111, 1988 Nov. 17; 1111 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1112, 1988 Nov. 17; 1112 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1113, 1988 Nov. 17; 1113 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1114, 1988 Nov. 24; 1114 (Item 21)
    New York City; kitchen window views; Chinese poets
  - Contact sheet 1115, 1988 Nov. 24; 1115 (Item 21)
    New York City; Thanksgiving at Eugene and Connie Brooks' house
  - Contact sheet 1116, 1988 Dec. 2; 1116 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1117, 1988 Dec. 4; 1117 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1118, 1988 Dec. 4; 1118 (Item 21)
    New York City; Knitting Factory; Kerouac memorial
  - Contact sheet 1119, 1988 Dec. 4; 1119 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1120, 1988 Dec. 4; 1120 (Item 21)
    New York City; Knitting Factory; Kerouac memorial reading
  - Contact sheet 1121, 1988 Dec. 4; 1121 (Item 21)
    New York City; Knitting Factory; Kerouac memorial reading; kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 1122, 1988 Dec. 11; 1122 (Item 21)
    New York City; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; Allen Ginsberg in hospital
  - Contact sheet 1123, 1988 Dec. 11; 1123 (Item 21)
    New York City; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; Allen Ginsberg in hospital; Kerouac reading at Knitting Factory
  - Contact sheet 1124, 1988 Dec. 23; 1124 (Item 21)
    New York City; Christmas Eve
  - Contact sheet 1125, 1988 Dec. 25; 1125 (Item 21)
    New York City; Allen Ginsberg in hospital
  - Contact sheet 1126, 1988 Dec. 25; 1126 (Item 21)
    New York City; Bob Rosenthal reading at Kerouac memorial at Knitting Factory
  - Contact sheet 1127, 1988 Dec. 26; 1127 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1128, 1988 Nov. 26; 1128 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1129, 1988 Nov. 26; 1129 (Item 21)
    New York City; Chanting Buddhist Priests from Tibet
  - Contact sheet 1130, 1988 Dec. 29; 1130 (Item 21)
    Mark Ewert and BH
  - Contact sheet 1131, 1989 Jan. 1; 1131 (Item 21)
    New York City; dumpling restaurant downstairs Chinatown; Allen Ginsberg self portrait
  - Contact sheet 1132, 1989 Jan. 6; 1132 (Item 21)
    New York City; kitchen window views; Mary Help of Christians Church window; filmmaker at St. Marks Church New Years Day reading
  - Contact sheet 1133, 1989 Jan. 6; 1133 (Item 21)
    New York City; kitchen window views; Mary Help of Christians Church window; Kush of Cloud House; Brooklyn student Angelo Branford visiting while I was sick; funeral across the street
    Angelo Branford
  - Contact sheet 1134, 1989 Jan. 10; 1134 (Item 21)
    New York City; Kush of Cloud House; funeral at Mary Help of Christians Church
  - Contact sheet 1135, 1989 Jan. 15; 1135 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1136, 1989 Jan. 20; 1136 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1137, 1989 Jan. 29; 1137 (Item 21)
    New York City; kitchen window views; subway scenes; dentist visit
  - Contact sheet 1138, 1989 Feb. 1; 1138 (Item 21)
    New York City; shrine
  - Contact sheet 1139, 1989 Feb. 3; 1139 (Item 21)
    New York City; Hillsburgh; Allen Ginsberg self portrait
  - Contact sheet 1140, 1989 Feb. 6; 1140 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1141, 1989 Feb. 10; 1141 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1142, 1989 Jan. 21; 1142 (Item 21)
    "Salt Lake, UT; New York City; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 1143, 1989 Feb. 14; 1143 (Item 21)
    "New York City; Philadelphia, PA; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; Philadelphia skyline"
  - Contact sheet 1144, 1989 Feb. 27; 1144 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1145, 1989 Mar. 1; 1145 (Item 21)
    Norman Mailer; Jayne Cortez
  - Contact sheet 1146.1, 1989 Mar. 1; 1146.1 (Item 21)
    New York City; kitchen window views; Mary Help of Christians Church window; street scenes
  - Contact sheet 1146.2, 1989 Mar. 10; 1146.2 (Item 21)
    COLOR: New York City
  - Contact sheet 1147, 1989 Mar. 18; 1147 (Item 21)
    New York City; city skyline
  - Contact sheet 1148, 1989 Mar. 20; 1148 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1149, 1989 Mar. 21; 1149 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1150, 1989 Mar. 29; 1150 (Item 21)
  - Contact sheet 1151, 1989 Apr. 3; 1151 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1152, 1989 Apr. 6; 1152 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1153.1, 1989 Apr. 8; 1153.1 (Item 22)
    New York City; Pyramid Club; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; Mary Help of Christians Church window; street scenes
  - Contact sheet 1153.2, 1989 Apr. 10; 1153.2 (Item 22)
    New York City; Audrey Lorde lecturing; Pyramid Club; Washington Square Arch
    Audre Lorde; Marie Buncombe; B
  - Contact sheet 1153.3, 1989 Apr. 13; 1153.3 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1153.4, 1989 Apr. 14; 1153.4 (Item 22)
    "New York City, North Carolina?; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1153.5, 1989 Apr. 14; 1153.5 (Item 22)
    North Carolina?; William Burroughs at Duke?
    Duke?; Burroughs, William S.
  - Contact sheet 1153.6, 1989 Apr. 14; 1153.6 (Item 22)
    "North Carolina?; New York City; Paterson, NJ; William Burroughs at Duke?; kitchen window views; Edith Ginsberg and Beverley Isis at the falls"
    Duke?
  - Contact sheet 1153.7, 1989 Apr. 19; 1153.7 (Item 22)
    "New York City; Paterson, NJ; Grand Rapids; Edith Ginsberg and Beverley Isis at the falls"
  - Contact sheet 1153.8, 1989 Apr. 20; 1153.8 (Item 22)
    Grand Rapids; street scenes
  - Contact sheet 1154.1, 1989 May 3; 1154.1 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1154.2, 1989 May 6; 1154.2 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1154.3, 1989 May 6; 1154.3 (Item 22)
    New York City; St. Mark's Church
  - Contact sheet 1154.4, 1989 May 6; 1154.4 (Item 22)
    Whalen, Philip
  - Contact sheet 1154.5, 1989 May 6; 1154.5 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1154.6, 1989 May 7; 1154.6 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1155, 1989 May 9; 1155 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1156, 1989 May 12; 1156 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1157, 1989 May 15; 1157 (Item 22)
    "New York City; Cherry Valley, NY; farmhouse"
  - Contact sheet 1158, 1989 May 15; 1158 (Item 22)
    Gwendolyn Brooks
  - Contact sheet 1159, 1989 May 16; 1159 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1160, 1989 May 17; 1160 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1161, 1989 May 17; 1161 (Item 22)
    New York City; American Academy
  - Contact sheet 1162, 1989 May 22; 1162 (Item 22)
    Rosa Von Praunheim
  - Contact sheet 1163, 1989 May 22; 1163 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1164, 1989 May 23; 1164 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1165, 1989 May 23; 1165 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1166, 1989 May 30; 1166 (Item 22)
    New York City; kitchen window views; Tompkins Square; street scenes
  - Contact sheet 1167, 1989 May 31; 1167 (Item 22)
    New York City; street scenes; PEN Club
  - Contact sheet 1168, 1989 June 3; 1168 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1169, 1989 June 9; 1169 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1170, 1989 June 10; 1170 (Item 22)
    New York City; Mary Help of Christians Church window; Abbie Hoffman picnic
  - Contact sheet 1171, 1989 June 11; 1171 (Item 22)
  - Contact sheet 1172, 1989 June 16; 1172 (Item 22)